http://www.brownmac.com/en/privacy-policy

Follow Us facebook twitter linkedin youtube
Español Português English
+44 (0)330 221 1106 Contact
Brown McFarlane - Steel Stockholders UK | Structural Steel
About UsHistoryCorporate VideoCapabilityCorporate ResponsibilityCareersMeet The TeamQualityProductsStainless Steel PlateDuplex Stainless SteelSuper Duplex Stainless SteelPressure Vessel SteelBoiler Plate SteelProcurement AssistanceQuenched and Tempered SteelAbrasion Resistant SteelHigh Yield Cold Forming Steel Plate460 Yield Steel PlateArmour PlateChrome Moly PlateOffshore & Structural Steel PlateHIC Steel PlateWeather Resistant Steel PlateServicesStainless Steel GradesProject ManagementPlate CuttingPlate ProcessingSteel Profiling & Weld PreparationGeneral ServicesPrecision EngineeringMarket SectorsEnergyWaste & RecyclingOffshore StructuresMining & QuarryingOil & GasGeneral EngineeringRenewablesPetrochemicalNuclearCivil Engineering & ConstructionDefenceMedia & DownloadsVideosBrochuresLatestNewsBlogCase Studies
About UsWe are Brown McFarlane Ltd, a wholly owned subsidiary of A.R. Brown McFarlane & Company Ltd., with company registration number SC121113. Our registered office is Unit 7 Lonmay Place, Panorama Business Village, Queenslie, Glasgow G33 4ER. We are a steel stockholder and processor of high quality metal plate and our main operation is based in Stoke-on-Trent.This policy sets out the basis on which we collect your personal information, or the personal information that you provide to us through our website, and how that information will be processed. By using our website, you consent to the processing of this information and you agree to be bound by this policy. You also confirm that all data provided by you is accurate.Information we gather about youWe obtain information about you when you use our website, for example, when you contact us about our products or services.We may collect the following information about you: Personal information that you provide when completing forms on the website. This might include your name, address, phone number, the company you work for and your e-mail address. Details of your visits to the website including but not limited to, your IP address and information regarding what pages are accessed and when. How we use this informationWe use information held about you in the following ways: To provide you with goods and services promoted by the website. For marketing purposes i.e. to send you information on products and services we believe you may be interested in. To carry out our obligations arising from any agreements between you and us. To notify you about important changes to our website. To ensure that the content from the website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your devices. For statistical data analysis where we may use your data to better understand our audience to improve our website, marketing and promotional work. We may keep your information for a reasonable period for these purposes.Disclosure of your informationIn addition to the uses above, we may disclose your personal information to third parties in the circumstances noted below: In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. If Brown McFarlane Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data it holds about its customers will be one of the transferred assets. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data to comply with any legal obligation, or to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of Brown McFarlane Ltd, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Your choicesYou have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing at any time by contacting us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..Additionally, you may opt out by post by writing to the following address: Brown McFarlane Ltd
Ladywell Works New Century Street
Hanley Stoke-on-Trent
Staffordshire ST1 5QH CookiesWe may collect information about your computer, including your IP address, operating system and browser type for system administration. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns and does not identify any individual.We use cookies on our website to distinguish you from other users of our website. A cookie is a small text file, which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile phone (referred to here as a "device") browser from a website's computer and stored on your device's hard drive. There are various types of cookies which perform different functions, such as remembering your preferences on our website or recording your browsing habits. The information recorded by the cookie is retrieved on the user’s next visit to the website.If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.If you would rather that we did not collect data in this way you can choose to accept all or some or reject cookies in your browser's privacy settings. Rejecting all cookies means that certain features cannot then be provided to you and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the website's features. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. For more information about cookies, including how to adjust your browser settings to reject cookies, visit www.aboutcookies.org.Someone else’s informationIf you provide us with information about another person, you confirm that they have appointed you to act for them, to consent to the processing of their personal data and you have informed them of our identity and the purposes (as set out above) for which their personal data will be processed.Dealing with your information safelyWe take appropriate measures to ensure that the information disclosed to us is kept secure, accurate and up to date and kept only for so long as is necessary for the purposes for which it is used.Other WebsitesOur website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.Your RightsYou are entitled to ask for a copy of the information we hold about you and to have any inaccuracies in your information corrected.Your DetailsQuestions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed. If your personal details change, if you change your mind about any of your marketing preferences or if you have any queries about how we use your information, please let us know by contacting us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. FaLang translation system by Faboba
Want to get in touch? Contact our team directly
Top Products
460 Yield High Strength Steel Plate
Abrasion/Wear Resistant Steel
Pressure Vessel Steel Plate
Boiler Plate Steel
HIC Steel Plate
Chrome Moly Steel Plate
Downloads Boiler and Pressure Vessel Steel 0.96mb View our full range of resources >
